ndesignweb.com 2016-10-22

# PRIVACY POLICY - NDESIGN

NDesign (the “Company”) is committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information that we collect at www.ndesignweb.com (the “Site”) to provide you with a superior shopping experience and to communicate with you about products, services, and promotions. This Privacy Policy provides information on the manner in which your personal information is processed and used on the Site. The Company uses your personal information only in ways that are compatible with this Privacy Policy.

##### Our Commitment To Privacy.

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

##### The Information We Collect.

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Site. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: name, address, email address and phone number. On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient’s address. We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. We offer gift-cards by which you can personalize a product you order for another person. Information you provide to us to create a gift-card is only used for that purpose, and it is only disclosed to the person receiving the gift. We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. You can register with our website if you would like to receive our catalog as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form. We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. Finally, we do not use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

##### Your Account.

When you place an order, we will ask you to set up “your account,” which includes your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number and expiration date. Using your account information, we will send you communications that we believe are relevant to you, including newsletters and e-mails. If you prefer not to receive optional e-mails or other communications from us, you may adjust your account to prevent such communications by clicking on “subscriptions” within “your account.” If you would like to review or revise the information we have in your account, you may access such information by clicking on the “your account” link on any screen.

If we receive updated account information from third parties, we may revise your account for you so that we can efficiently process your orders, deliver your packages or otherwise communicate with you. For example, we may receive customer information from our shippers. In addition, we may acquire customer names, e-mail addresses and mailing addresses for select mailings from third parties.

_Other Information You Provide:_ We collect additional information that you choose to give us. For example, you provide information to us when you complete surveys or contest entry forms, sign up for special discounts or coupons, communicate with us by e-mail, phone or otherwise, provide product reviews, or provide alternative delivery addresses.

##### Security.

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information collected online. When you place an order online, your personal information and credit card or debit card information are encrypted using PayPal encryption technology before being sent over the Internet. We use PayPal’s technology to prevent your information from being stolen or intercepted while being transferred to us. Your credit card information is always encrypted to keep it safe from hackers.

##### Cookies.

To personalize and enhance your browsing and shopping experience, we use a feature on your Internet browser called a cookie. Cookies are small files that your Web browser places on your computer’s hard drive. We use cookies to let us know that you are a prior customer and to retrieve certain information previously provided by you to us, so that you do not need to re-enter this information every time you shop at the site. Cookies also let us know how you found us (e.g., through a particular web site or advertisement). Cookies are not used to access information entered on the secure server. This information can be accessed only when you enter your name and password. If you choose to configure your browser to remove or reject our cookies, you may not be able to make purchases from our Site or take advantage of many of our features.

##### Unsolicited E-mail (SPAM).

Your privacy is very important to us. Be assured that, in accordance with this privacy policy, we do not sell or distribute our customer list to third parties. You should be aware, however, that unscrupulous marketers can sometimes “harvest” your e-mail address directly from your computer or another person’s address book or even obtain your e-mail address through programs that automatically search web pages and e-mail traffic for e-mail addresses.

Please note that all e-mail that originates from us will either display www.ndesignweb.com (HTML emails) or contain the Company copyright notice (text emails). In addition, our e-mails will contain our corporate address in Powell, Ohio. If you receive an unsolicited e-mail that you believe is connected with us in any way, please contact us by filling out the form on our Contact Page.

##### Children.

We do not sell products for purchase by children. We sell children’s products for purchase by adults. If you are under 18, you may use our Site only with the involvement of a parent or guardian. Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

##### Linked Web Sites.

Our Web stores may contain links to and from other sites operated and maintained by separate companies. We have no responsibility for linked Web sites (including the Web sites of participants in our associate program) and provide these links solely for the convenience and information of our visitors. The privacy policies of these sites may differ from our policy, so you should always review the privacy statement of each linked Web site you visit.

##### Your Consent.

By using our Site, you consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of information in accordance with the terms of this privacy policy. We reserve the right to modify or amend this policy at any time. If we ever change our privacy policy, we will post any changes on this page or send you an e-mail so that you are always aware of the information that we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Unless we clearly state otherwise, the changes to our privacy policy will affect only the information we collect after the effective date of the change.

##### How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information.

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging into your account and updating or removing your information 24 hours a day, 365 days a year. The Site uses 128 bit encrypting because we use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

##### How To Contact Us.

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 614.655.7 **WEB** (7932), or contact us by filling out the form on our [Contact Page](http://www.ndesignweb.com/contact/).
